Guide to the Ernst Weber Collection RG.033
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Writings
  - Subseries G: Notes
    - Untitled - 7a, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "General Discussion First Order Diff. Equ. Singularities and Char. - 8", undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Instability in Single Energy CTS (Arc) Sweep Circuit - 8a", undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "W107 Circuits with Trine-Varying Parameters (Linear) - 10", 1931-1932, 1936, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Double Energy-Nonlinear Oscillations (Direct Solution) - 11", undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Energy Circuits, Free Oscill. - Topology - 12", undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - "Oscillators Feedback (Harmonic) - 12a", undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Oscillators, Nonlinear (Inductance, Capacitance) - 12b", undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "... Nonlinear Oscillations Negative Resistance - 12c", undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "Forced Oscillations: Differing, General, Existence of Periodic Solutions - 13", undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - "W20 Ferro-Resonance 'Non-Linear Resonance' Double Energy CTS - 12a", undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "Topology Phase Space: Non Linear Circuits - 13b", undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "Transients Kryloft - Bogobiuboft - 14a", undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Applications of Integral Equations to the Solution of Nonlinear Electric Circuit Problems - 14a, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - "Method of Isoclines Lienard Construction Acceleration Plane - 14b", undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "Relaxation Oscillations - 15", undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - "Multivibrator -15a", undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - "Flip-Flop - 15e", 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - "W104 Subharmonic Resonance - 16", 1936-1952 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - "Hill's Equation (for stability) Mathien - 17", 1943, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "Singular Perturbation Problems - 18", 1946 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - "Stability Criteria General - 19", 1937, 1944, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - "Laplace Transform of Nonlinear Analysis", 1953-1956 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - "Complex Convolution Applied to Nonlinear Analysis (Differing Equations)", undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - "Conformal Spherdidal Loord: And Function Systems", 1944 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - "Vallise Notes", undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - "Additional Reference Material", 1949 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Derivation of a Linearized Solution of the Duffing Equation by the Complex Convolution Method, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Notes on philosophy, 1972-1973, 1979, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Notes on equations, 1936-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Notes on equations, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Complex Convolution", 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Notes for Thomas T. Goldsmith's 75th Birthday, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sonya Weber Bio Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Dr. Weber", 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Engineering Lecture Series, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Metamorphic and Periodic Fetuses, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - MIT Interdisciplinary Graduate Study Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Weber's calendar, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Notes on evolution, 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "System Science" Notes and Negatives, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "Fourier Integral Application to Circuit Theory", undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Four Pole Filter Transients", undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1965-1987 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Series III: Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn
  - Subseries A: Weber Inauguration as President
    - Inauguration/Dedication programs, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration press releases, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Inauguration of Ernst Weber - Rear Admiral Rickover speech, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Inaugural Address of Ernst Weber, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Dedication/Inauguration Committee memos, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Dedication/Inauguration Committee planning materials, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Dedication/Inauguration working materials, Alice Woller, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dedication/Inauguration invitations, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Inauguration congratulatory messages, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Inauguration correspondence, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Inauguration telegrams, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Inauguration acknowledgements from universities, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Inauguration acknowledgement from Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Convocation Honoring Weber
    - Convocation planning, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Weber emeritus announcement, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Weber convocation invitations, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Weber convocation, "Scientist as Politician", 1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Convocation program, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - A Bibliography for The Continuing Dialogue Convocation Honoring Dr. Ernst Weber, 1970 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence
    - Babbott, Frank, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Brakeley John Price Jones, Inc., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Inter-Office Correspondence and Memoranda
    - Inter-Office correspondence to departments, 1953-1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Memos to faculty and students, 1960-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Memos to the corporation, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Inter-Office correspondence and memos, 1970-1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries E: MRI and Weber Research Institute
    - "Microwave Research Institute, 1952-1964" (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "Microwave Research Institute, 1958-1965" (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - MRI Research reports, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - MRI Research reports, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - MRI Research reports, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - "Microwave Power Measurement", 1954 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Memoirs of the faculty of science and engineering Waseda University, Tokyo, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - MRI memos, 1953-1967 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - MRI Symposia, 1952-1959 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - MRI Symposia, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - "Historical Notes on Microwaves", 1954 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Weber course notes on Non-Linear Systems, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Microwave notes, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - History of the Microwave Research Institute, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - MRI Patents U.S. binder, 1950-1957 (Box 10, Item 1)
    - MRI Patents Foreign binder, 1945-1956 (Box 10, Item 2)
    - Dedication of the Weber Research Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Weber Research Institute Advisory Council, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MRI monographs volumes 1-24, 1952-1976 (Volume 1-24)
  - Subseries F: Academic Departments, Programs, and Research
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Annual Reports, 1952-1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. publications, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1942-1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic Research and Development Co. Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Department of Chemistry, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Sandia Corporation Project Report, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Sandia Corporation Project Report, 1959-1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Ray-O-Vac Company Fellowship Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering, Ray-O-Vac Company Fellowship Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Polymer Research Institute, 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Transmission Lines: Ideal Cable, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Municipal Civil Service Exam, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Final Report for OSRD Contract OEMsr-335, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Discrete System Concepts Project (NSF), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering Reprints, 1936-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering, Optimal Stochastic Control Theory- A Short Course, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Office of Telecommunications Management, "Technological Trends in Telecommunications", 1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Electrical Engineering Department History, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Department of Mathematics Undergraduate Research Participation, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Department of Urban Transportation Planning, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Class notes: Mechanics and Thermodynamics of real Gases (Course 0681), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kurt O. Friedrichs, Mathematical Lectures of Electromagnetic Theory, 1973 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - "Rob't Seeley Electric Design", circa 1920 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - "Elec Design", circa 1940 (Box 11, Item 3)
    - Long Island Graduate Center, Aerospace Research Laboratories, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Graduate Center and Sperry Gyroscope Co., undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The Science Development Program of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - PIB Patent Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Professional Degrees Record of Activities, 1937-1948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Final report on the L.A. Dreyfus Co. Research Project, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Progress Report of the Protein Structure Project, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Industrial Waste-Heat Recovery Methods - Final report, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation Proposals for New Facilities, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - National Science Foundation Grants, 1965-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Glass slides in wooden box
  - Subseries G: Budgets and Faculty/Student Data
    - "Budget Planning", 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Campus space analysis and costs, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Budget summary, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Budget Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Inter-Office correspondence - Budget, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee and budget reports, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Financial examinations, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Student enrollment and cost data, 1960-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Comparative cost studies - students, 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Comparative research - grants, 1952-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Faculty and department data, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Faculty lists and bios, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Faculty salaries, 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Organizational chart and corporation members, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic AAUP Chapter (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Weber budget notes, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Weber budget notes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Notes on budgets and salaries, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Subseries H: Press Releases and Marketing
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Albert E. Sobel Prize, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Joshua W. Sill Award, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases - Weber, local visits, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Polytechnic Press Releases, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - The Role of Polytechnic in Long Island's Future, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Polytechnic advertising campaigns, 1975-1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Polytechnic brochure packet, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Polytechnic departmental brochures, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - PIB visitor's folder, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic brochures, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic brochures, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Subseries I: Publications
    - Annual Reports, 1931, 1971, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Report on financial statements, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - President's Report, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Gifts to the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Project Rita, Annual Report, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Self-Study Report, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic Faculty News - Robert Van Valer, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic Faculty Newsletters, 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Poly Men - President Ernst Weber: A Message to Poly Alumni, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Cable, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Flyers, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Subseries J: Events
    - Inaugural Address of Dr. Ernst Weber, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Address at Polytechnic Alumni Dinner, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Establishment of Polytechnic's Long Island Center for Graduate Study and Research, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Introduction of Dr. Herman F. Mark, commencement, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Student convocation, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Commencement address, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Commencement address, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Greetings to the class of 1960 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Commencement address, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Commencement address, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "Egalitarianism or Individualism?" commencement address, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Long Island Center, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Honorary degree to Charles P. Snow, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Welcoming Address, 15th Symposium, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Our Dedicated Task, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - What a Civic Center Means to Brooklyn and the Nation, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Speeches, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Symposia, 1956-1963 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - 1973 Commencement Program with notes to Weber (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bugliarello Inauguration, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Dedications, Benefits, and Honor Ceremonies, 1968-1984 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Subseries K: Photographs
    - Weber Inauguration and Rogers Hall Dedication, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Weber Inauguration and Rogers Hall Dedication, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Proposed Academic Tower, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Poly photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Poly photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Poly photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Poly negatives, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Subseries L: President's Mailing List
    - President's Mailing List alphabetical, 1969 August (Box 14, Item 1)
    - President's Mailing List sub-list, 1969 August (Box 14, Item 2)
    - President's Mailing List alphabetical, 1970 March (Box 14, Item 3)
    - President's Mailing List sub-list, 1970 March (Box 14, Item 4)
    - President's Mailing List (missing cover), 1970 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - Subseries M: The Weber Collection
    Biographical / Historical
    The Weber Collection was the name given to a collection of books from Weber's personal library, which he donated to Dibner Library in 1991.
    - Weber Collection Notes, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Polytechnic University: The Weber Collection, 1991 May 31 (Box 15, Item 1)
    - The Weber Collection, 1996 October 9 (Box 15, Item 2)
    - The Weber Collection (blue binder), undated (Box 15, Item 3)
    - The Weber Collection with book appraisal, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Item 4)
- Series IV: Mergers
  - Subseries A: SUNY
    - Chronology of a possible PIB-SUNY merger, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Chronology of a possible PIB-SUNY merger, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Affiliation with State University: History of events, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Budget, estimated construction costs, and SUNY notes, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Dr. E. Weber" financial reports, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Terman Report on The Polytechnic, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Operation SUNY, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - PIB Long Island Center report, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn: Continuance or Condemnation, A study by the Senate Finance Minority, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn: Analysis of the Financial Future, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Documents for Negotiations", 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Documentary", 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "E. Weber" PIB and New York State, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ernst Weber - SUNY State Education Department, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Gould, Allen, Marshall, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - SUNY merger notes, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - SUNY merger notes, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - SUNY merger correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Weber correspondence and notes, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - SUNY merger memos, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Corporation Reference Material", 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Corp. Ad Hoc Committee", 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Corporation and Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Planning Board, Polytechnic", 1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Corporation President's Folder", 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - PIB and SUNY merger press releases, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - PIB and New York State merger proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Proposals of the Downstate Medical and Technological University of SUNY, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Agreements between PIB and SUNY, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: NYU
    - NYU merger correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - PIB Board minutes and NYU merger, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York academic plan, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "PINY Out, Polytechnic In," Polytechnic News, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - President's reports to trustees and faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "Planning and Evaluating an Academic Merger and Making it Work", 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - NYU school of Engineering History, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Series V: Publications
  - Subseries A: Newsletters and Advertising
    - Newsletters, 1968-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Washington Newsletter on Adult Education", 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Press releases, 1958-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Bulletins, 1925, 1950, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - WNEW-TV 40th anniversary, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Papers and Drafts
    - Papers on finite antennas, 1933-1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Papers on linear and non-linear systems, 1949-1957 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Radiation Laboratory technical report, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Information Theory Part I and Information Theory Part II by Stanford Goldman, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Current Issues in the Transfer and Transmission of Information by D.G. Fink and J.J. Lloyd, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Papers, Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1943-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Papers, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1956-1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Papers, Harvard University, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Papers, University of Illinois, 1949, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Papers, United States universities, 1953, 1957, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Papers, German universities, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Papers, Japanese universities, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Papers, Canadian universities, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Papers, professional organizations, 1959-1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Papers, industry, 1937-1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Papers, miscellaneous, 1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1968-1986 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1971-1983 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1971-1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - German language publications, 1932-1953 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - German language publications, 1953-1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - German language publications, 1939-1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - German language publications, 1951-1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - French language publications, 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Magazine and Newspaper Clippings
    - American Scientist, 1975-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - The American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Engineering Education, 1970-1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Invention and Technology, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Journal of Applied Physics, 1942-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Journal of Applied Physics, 1946-1952 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Physics Today, 1953-1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Physics Today, 1970-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Physics Today, 1970-1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Physics Today, 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Physics Today, 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Physics Today, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Quarterly of Applied Mathematics, 1956-1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Science, 1956-1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Science, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Science, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Science, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Science, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Science, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Science, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Science, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Science, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Science, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Science, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Science, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Science, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Science and Technology, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Science News, 1974-1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1920-1939 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1940-1949 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1950-1959 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Journal reprints and clippings, 1987, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Plasma physics and electromagnetics clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Soviet-USA education clippings and notes, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Magazine clippings, 1963-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Magazine clippings, 1972-1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1959-1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings, Polytechnic, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)